corporette.com 2015-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Corporette.com

[](http://dailydropcap.com/)orporette takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site and/or register for our e-mail newsletter.

**Personal Information**  
When you leave a comment at Corporette or subscribe to any of our e-mail newsletters, we may collect personal details about you. If you correspond with us by e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages, your e-mail address and our responses. Corporette will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent or as required by law, except to a third party as required to help us send your information to you. Upon request, we will provide you with the information that we maintain about you.

**Non-Personal Information**  
We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising with Corporette or our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage Information**  
When you visit the site, we also collect web site usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer’s IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and, if you arrived at Corporette via a link from another website, the URL of the linking page. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver content to you.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
If we ever send you an e-mail that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request to receive no future notices.

**Cookies**  
Corporette and some of our partners may make use of cookies (small text tiles placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server). They are used to collect non-personal traffic information such as the number of visits to our site and pages visited. This information will only be used to assess how subscribers are using our services so that we may better serve you. This data will also allow us to manage the functionality of the site, determine which site features are most popular, and show you relevant content and advertising. Corporette will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.  
You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time.  
Further information on the use of cookies can be found at:  
http://www.cookiecentral.com.

**E-mails**  
Corporette uses reputable third parties to deliver the e-mails you will receive from our site if you subscribe to our e-mail newsletters or have chosen to receive information about Corporette products and offers. These third parties use unique identifiers and invisible images (often called “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) to perform message open sensing, message format sensing, and clickthrough sensing on behalf of Corporette in order to bring you more relevant information.  
Content and some ad services in these e-mails are provided by Corporette or a third party ad server.  
****

**Ads**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Links to Other Sites  
**Although Corporette may provide links to third party sites, we are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites nor do we endorse these sites. Please review each site’s privacy policy to determine their use of information.

**Security**  
Corporette has appropriate measures in place to ensure that users’ personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within the Corporette server environment.  
Occasions will arise when customer information is passed outside Corporette to other data processors but they will only act upon instruction from Corporette in order to perform the services required.

**Modification to this Policy**  
Corporette may change this privacy policy. Any changes will be reflected on this privacy policy page. If you are concerned about how your information will be used, you should check back at this privacy policy page periodically.

**Contac** **t**  
If you should have any questions about our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://corporette.com/contact/).
